Guide to the Marvyn Scudder Collection of Corporate Documents,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
Marvyn Scudder Collection of Corporate Documents,
1827-1950s
Scudder, Marvyn, 1876-1935, collector
514 linear ft. (411 record storage cartons).
Columbia University. Rare Book & Manuscript Library Butler Library, 6th Fl. East, 535 West 114th St., New York, NY. 10027
7229539
Marvyn Scudder, the editor of the Marvyn Scudder Manual of Extinct and Obsolete Companies and the country's most famous stock detective, donated the collection to Columbia in 1921. The collection contains more than 3,000,000 pages of documentary material on thousands of United States and foreign corporations. Although there is a small number of annual reports in the collection, reports from almost 5000 companies are available in the complementary collection of Historical Corporate Annual Reports available from Columbia University's Watson Library of Business and Economics.
History
Begun in 1885 by Moses L. Scudder, head of the Investor's Agency in New York, the collection was inherited by Marvyn Scudder, editor of the "Marvyn Scudder Manual of Extinct and Obsolete Companies" and the country's most famous stock detective. He gave the collection to the Business Library in 1921. Particularly strong in documents from railroads, mining companies and New York City real estate companies, the Scudder Collection has a complete file of material on the Union Pacific Railroad that includes the original offering statements.
The Marvyn Scudder Collection of corporate documents is believed to be the largest of its kind with more than 3,000,000 pages of documentary material on the financial history and organization of thousands of United States and foreign corporations.
Scope and Content
Includes communications to shareholders, indentures, prospectuses, reorganization plans, annual reports, and other corporate instruments dating from 1827.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by corporate name.
Subjects
Scudder, Marvyn, 1876-1935.; Corporations--United States.; Mineral industries--Finance.; Business history.; Railroads--History.
Access Restrictions
The finding aid for the Marvyn Scudder Collection of Corporate Documents lists only the first and last company in each box, but Columbia University's Watson Library of Business and Economics maintains a 48-drawer card catalog in a separate room that lists every company in the collection. Patrons who wish to consult the card catalog for the Scudder Collection should request access to that catalog specifically from the Watson Library reference desk.
The Watson Library website also provides access to a spreadsheet of a complete list of every report in the Historical Corporate Annual Reports collection, as well as a two-drawer card catalog of the same reports. Patrons who wish to consult the card catalog for Historical Annual Reports should request it at the Watson Library reference desk. (Be advised that because of Mr. Scudder’s fame, this catalog is sometimes confusingly also known as the “Scudder Annual Reports” card catalog.)
This collection is located off-site. You will need to request this material at least twenty-four (24) hours in advance to use the collection in the Rare Book and Manuscript Library reading room.
Acquisition
Business Library Transfer 2004.
Selected Related Material-- at Columbia
Scudder Corporate Annual Reports
- Alphabetical Files
  - A & K Petroleum Company TO Adams Clark Building Corp. (Ill) (Box 1)
  - Adams Engineering Co. TO Aero Underwriters Corp. (Box 2)
  - Aeronautical Industries Inc. TO Air Marshal Corp. (Box 3)
  - Air-O-Cel Industries Inc. TO Alabama-Tennessee Natural Gas Co. (Box 4)
  - Alabama Traction Light & Power Co, Ltd. TO Alberta, Province of Canada (Box 5)
  - Alberta Wheat Pool TO Allentown Terminal Railroad Co. (PA) (Box 6)
  - Allergan Pharmaceuticals TO Allis (Louis) Co. (WI) (Box 7)
  - Allis-Charmers Mfg. Co. (DEL) TO Aluminum Company of America (Box 8)
  - Aluminum Company of Canada, Ltd. TO American Aircraft Company (DEL) (Box 9)
  - American Alfalfa Products Co. TO American Break Shoe Company (Box 10)
  - American Brake Shoe & Foundry Company TO American Credit Indemnity Company of New York (Box 11)
  - American Cryogentcs, Inc. TO American Fram Products Company (Box 12)
  - American Felt Company (NJ) TO American Heat, Light & Power Company (ME) (Box 13)
  - American Hide & Leather Company TO American Locomotive Company (Box 14)
  - American London & Empire Corp. TO American Public Services Company (Box 15)
  - American Public Utilities Company TO American Security Company of Bedford Indiana (Box 16)
  - American Seeding Machine Company TO American Sumatra Tobacco Corporation (Box 17)
  - American Sumatra Tobacco Corp. TO American Title & Insurance Company (Box 18)
  - American Tobacco Company TO American Water Works & Electric Co. Inc (VA) (Box 19)
  - American Water Works & Electric Company, 1932-1949 TO American Yvette Company, Inc. (Box 20)
  - American Zinc & Lead Mining & Milling Co. TO Anchor Post products, Inc. (Box 21)
  - Anchor Precision Corp. TO Ann Arbor Railroad Co. (Box 22)
  - Annie Consolidate Mining Co. TO Arista Truck Renmting Corp. (Box 23)
  - Family Finance Corp [Name cahnged to Arista] TO Armco Steele Corp. (Box 24)
  - Armin Poly Film Corp. TO Arwood Corp. (Box 25)
  - Arwood Precision Casting Corp. TO Associated Gas & Electric Co. (Box 26)
  - Associated Gas & Electric Co. TO Associated Sudents, Univ. of Washington (Box 27)
  - Associated Telephone & Telegraph TO Athens Railway & Electric Co. (Box 28)
  - Athey Truss Wheel Co. TO Atlantic City Electric Co. (Box 29)
  - Atlantic City Gas Co. TO Atlas Assurance Co. (Box 30)
  - Atlas Chemical Industries TO Australion Iron & Steele (Box 31)
  - Austro-American Silver Copper & General Mining Association TO Ayrshire Patoka Colliers Corp. (Box 32)
  - Aztec Land & Cattle Co. TO Bali Co. (Box 33)
  - Ball Engine Co. TO Bamm Corp. (Box 34)
  - Banca Commerciale Italiana TO Bandar Rubber Moatschappij (Box 35)
  - Band-It Company TO Bank of Scotland (Box 36)
  - Bank of Silesian Landowners Assn., Breslau TO Barahona Sugar Corp. (Box 37)
  - Barbara Lynn Stories Inc. TO Barrington Court (Box 38)
  - Barry Apartments TO Bayless Pulp & Paper Company (Box 39)
  - Bayly Manufacturing Co TO Bellingham, Washington (City of) (Box 40)
  - Bellows Falls Hydro-Electric Corp. TO Beth Warehouse (Box 41)
  - Bethleham City Warter Co. TO Birmingham Realty Co. (Box 42)
  - Birmingham Small Arms CO. To Bohn Aluminum & Brass Corp. (Box 43)
  - Bohn Refrigerator Co. TO Boston & Montana Development Co. (Box 44)
  - Boston & Montana Milling & Power Co. TO Botany Mills Inc. (Box 45)
  - Botany Industries Inc. TO Brazos Oil Corp. (Box 46)
  - Brazos River Gas Co. TO British-American Ball Nozzle Co. (Box 47)
  - British-American Bank Note Company, Ltd. TO Broadway Department Store, Inc. (Box 48)
  - Broadway Exchange Corp. TO Brooklyn-Manhattan Transit Corp. (Box 49)
  - Brooklyn-Manhattan Transit Corp TO Brush Moore Newspaper (Box 50)
  - Bryant & Chapman Co. TO Buffalo Elevators, Inc. (Box 51)
  - Buffalo Gas Co. TO Burmah Oil Company Ltd. (Box 52)
  - Burmeister & Wain, Engineers & Shipbuilders, Ltd. TO C & K Brewing Co. (Box 53)
  - C & R Hotel Company TO California Excelsior Oil Company (Box 54)
  - California Federal Savings & Loan Association TO Camaguey Company, Ltd. (Box 55)
  - Camaguey Sugar Company TO Canadian Colonial Airways Inc. (Box 56)
  - Canadian Consolidated Felt Company TO Canadian Propane Ltd. (Box 57)
  - Canadian Property Co. TO Capitol Reef Uranium Corp. (Box 58)
  - Capitol Southwest Corp. TO Carter, William Company (Box 59)
  - Carolina & Northwestern Railway Co. TO Cellulose Products Inc. (Box 60)
  - Celotex Company TO Central Fule Oil Company (Box 61)
  - Central Funding Corp TO Centyral Leather Company (Box 62)
  - Central Leather Company TO Central Paper Company (Box 63)
  - Central Paper Company, Inc. TO Central States Investment Trust, Inc. (Box 64)
  - Central States Power & Light Corp. TO Cessna Aircraft Company (Box 65)
  - Chadwick Brass Company TO Chase National Bank Annual Reports, 1941-50 (Box 66)
  - Charlevoix Realty Corp. TO Chelsea Realty Company (Box 67)
  - Chemcell Limited TO Cheraw & Darlington Railroad Company (Box 68)
  - Cherm TO Chesapeake Corp. (Box 69)
  - Chesapeake Corp. TO Chiacgo & Eastern Illinois Railway Company (Box 70)
  - Chicago & Eastern Illinois RR. Co. TO Chiago & Southern Airlines Inc. (Box 71)
  - Chicago & Eastern Illinois RR. Co. TO Chiago & Southern Airlines Inc. (Box 72)
  - Chicago Economic Fuel Gas Company TO Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad Co. (Box 73)
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul Railway Co. TO Chicago Railways Company (Box 74)
  - Chicago Rapid Transit Company TO Chicago Suburban Gas and Electric Co. (Box 75)
  - Chicago Subway Co. TO Childs Food Stores, Inc. (Box 76)
  - Child's Co. TO Cincinnati, Findlay and Fort Wayne Railway Company (Box 77)
  - Cincinnati Gas and Electric Co. TO Cities Service Company (Box 78)
  - Cities Service Power and Light Co. TO City National Building Company (Box 79)
  - City of Newcastle Water Company TO Clevland-cliffs Iron Company (Box 80)
  - Clevland, Columbus, Cincinnati and Indianapolis Railway Co. TO Coca-Cola Bottling Co. of New York Inc. (Box 81)
  - Coca-Cola Company TO Colorado, Columbus and Mexican R.R (Box 82)
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Co. TO Columbia Steel and Shafting Co. (Box 83)
  - Columbia- Southern Chemical Corp. TO Columbus Packing Co. (Box 84)
  - Columbus Power Company TO Commonwealth and Southern Corp. (Box 85)
  - Commonwealth and Southern Corp. TO Community Power and Light Company (Box 86)
  - Community Public Service Company TO Connecticut General Life Insurance Company (Box 87)
  - Connecticut Humane Society TO Consolidated Chemical Industries (Box 88)
  - Consolidated Chemical Industries TO Consolidated Fuel Company (Box 89)
  - Consolidated Gas Company of Baltimore City TO Consolidated Laundries Corp. (Box 90)
  - Consolidated Lead and Zinc Co. TO Consumers Power Company (Box 91)
  - Consumers Public Service Co. TO Continental Telephone Co. (Box 92)
  - Continental Typewriter Co. TO Com Products Refining Co. (Box 93)
  - Corning Glass Works TO Credit Foncier of America Inc. (Box 94)
  - Credit Italiano TO Crown Cork and Seal Company Ltd. (Box 95)
  - Crown Cork and Seal Company of Baltimore City TO Cuban Sugar Mills Corp. (Box 96)
  - Cuban Telephone Company TO Cushing Petroleum Corp. (Box 97)
  - Cushman Food Co., Inc. TO Dana Corp. (Box 98)
  - Danac Real Estate Investment Corp. TO Daystrom Inc. (Box 99)
  - Dayton Airplane Engine Co. TO Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad Co. (Box 100)
  - Delaware National Bank TO Denver and Salt Lake Western Railroad Co. (Box 101)
  - Denver Chicago Trucking Co. Inc. TO Detroit, Almont and Northern Railroad Co. (Box 102)
  - Denver and Canada Tunnel Co. TO Detroit Trust Co. (Box 103)
  - Detroit United Railway TO Distillers Securities Corp. (Box 104)
  - Distilling and Cattle Feeding Co. TO Dominion Radiator and Boiler Co. Ltd. (Box 105)
  - Dominion Reduction Co. Ltd. TO Dry Dock East Broadway and Battery R.R. Co. (Box 106)
  - Dry Dock Savings Institution TO Eagle Harbor Copper Co. (Box 107)
  - Eagle-Picher Co. to Eastern Aircraft Corp. (Box 108)
  - Eastern Airlines Inc. to Easy Washing Machine Corp. (Box 109)
  - Eaton and Howard Management Fund A-1 TO Edwards Dental Supply Co. (Box 110)
  - Egyptian Lacquer Manufacturing Co. TO Electric Bond and Share Co. (Box 111)
  - Electric Cable Co. TO 1133 Park Avenue Apartment Building (Box 112)
  - Eleven West Forty Second Street, Inc. TO Emerson Shoe Stores Co. (Box 113)
  - Emerson Truck and Tractor Co. TO Energie Electrique du Littoral Mediterraneen (Box 114)
  - Energie Electrique du Nord de la France TO Erie Railroad Co. - Prospectuses (Box 115)
  - Erie Railroad Co. TO Europe on Wheels, Inc. (Box 116)
  - European and North American Railway TO Fairbanks, Morse and Co. (Box 117)
  - Fairchild Aviation Corp. TO Farrell Foundry and Machine Co. (Box 118)
  - Farrington Manufacuring Co. TO Federal Public Service Corp. (Box 119)
  - Federal Public Utilities Co. TO Fidelity Finance Corp., Doing Business as American Finance Co. (Box 120)
  - Fidelity Fund, Inc. TO Fireman's Fund Indemnity Co. (Box 121)
  - Fireman's Fund Insurance Co. TO First National Bank, Morengo, IA (Box 122)
  - First National Bank (Marlow, OK) TO Fisher Building (Box 123)
  - Fisher Flouring Mills TO Flintridge Hotel Co. (Box 124)
  - Flo-Mix Fertilizers Corp. TO Flour City Ornamental Iron Co. (Box 125)
  - Flour Mills of America, Inc. TO Forstmann Woolen Co. (Box 126)
  - Fort Collins Consolidated Royalties, Inc. TO Foundation Securities Corp. (Box 127)
  - Foundation Trust Shares TO H.H. Franklin Manufacturing Co. (Box 128)
  - Franklin Mining Company TO Fuller Brush Co. (Box 129)
  - Fuller Building TO Gardens Apartments Inc. (Box 130)
  - Gardner- Denver Co. TO General Acceptance Corp. (Box 131)
  - General Acceptance Corp. TO General Equities Inc. (Box 132)
  - General Electric Overseas Capital Corp. TO General Optical Co., Inc. (Box 133)
  - General Outdoor Advertising Co. TO General Steamship Corp. (Box 134)
  - General Steel Casting Corp. TO Georgia and Florida Railroad (Box 135)
  - Georgia Florida and Alabama Railroad Co. TO Gibsons Inc. (Box 136)
  - Gero Metallurgical Corp. TO Glenwyn Apts. (Box 137)
  - Glidden Co. TO Goldfield Noble Mining Co. (Box 138)
  - Goldfield Peerless Mining Co. TO Goodyear Tire and Rubber Co. (Box 139)
  - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Co. TO Grand Rapids Edison Co. (Box 140)
  - Grand Rapids Gas Light Co. TO Gray's Point Terminal Railway Co. (Box 141)
  - Graybear Building TO Great Northern Iron Ore Properties (Box 142)
  - Great Northern Majestic Building Corp. TO Green Bay, Winona and St. Paul R.R. Co. (Box 143)
  - Greenboro TO Greyhound Lines, Inc. (Box 144)
  - Greyhound Corp. TO Guaranty Title and Trust Corp. (Box 145)
  - Guaranty Trust and Savings Bank TO Gum and Sweetmeat Co. (Box 146)
  - Gundrum (H.F.) Co. TO Hallicrafters Co. (Box 147)
  - Halliday Lithograph Corp. TO Hanlon and Goodman Co. (Box 148)
  - Hanlon-Gregory Galvanizing Co. TO Hart-Carter Co. (Box 149)
  - Hart Coal Co. TO Havana Electric and Utilities Co. (Box 150)
  - Havana Electric Railway Co. TO Hearst Brisbane Properties (Box 151)
  - Hearst Building TO Hercules Petroleum Co. (Box 152)
  - Hercules Powder Co. TO Highland Spruce Co. (Box 153)
  - Highland Telephone Co. TO Hocking Valley Railway Co. (Box 154)
  - Hodge Iron Co. TO Home Mortgage Investment Co. (Box 155)
  - Home Oil Co., Ltd. TO Hotel Lennox (Box 156)
  - Hotel Lexington TO Household Finance Corp. (Box 157)
  - Household Finance Corp. TO Hudson and Long Island Traction Co. (Box 158)
  - Hudson and Manhattan Co. TO Hunter Machinery Co. (Box 159)
  - Hunter Steel Co. TO Hydraulic-Press Brick Co. (Box 160)
  - Hydraulic- Pressed Steel Co. TO Idaho State Life Insurance Co., Ltd. (Box 161)
  - Idaho Yellow Jacket Gold Mining Co. TO Illinios Pacific Glass Corp. (Box 162)
  - Illiniois Packing Co. TO Income Leasehold Co. (Box 163)
  - Income Trust Shares TO Indiana Consumers Gas and By-Products Co. (Box 164)
  - Indiana, Decatur and Western Railway Co. TO Indiana Truck Corp. (Box 165)
  - Indiana Union Traction Co. TO Industrial Advancement Corp. of Utica (Box 166)
  - Industrial and General Trust, Ltd. TO Inland Express Co. (Box 167)
  - Inland Gas Corp. TO Insuranceshares Corp. (Box 168)
  - Insuranceshares Trust Certificates TO Interborough- Metropolitan Co. (Box 169)
  - Interborough Personal Loan Co. TO Interborough Rapid Transit Co. (Box 170)
  - Interborough Rapid Transit Co. TO International Carbon Corp. (Box 171)
  - International Carriers, Ltd. TO International and Great Northern Railway Co. (Box 172)
  - International and Great Northern Railway Co. TO International Match Corp. (Box 173)
  - International Match Realization Corp. TO Int'l Okonite Corp. (Box 174)
  - Int'l Ordinance Co. TO Int'l Safety Razor Corp. (Box 175)
  - Int'l Salt Corp. TO Int'l Water Co. (Box 176)
  - Int'l Waterways Navigation TO Interstate Public Utilities Corp. (Box 177)
  - Interstate Railway TO Investors Fund Inc. (Box 178)
  - Investors Management Fund, Inc. TO Iowa Nebraska Public Service Co. (Box 179)
  - Iowa Planning Company TO Irvine Life Boat Handler Co. (Box 180)
  - Irving Trust Co. TO (J&B) Ivey Company (Box 181)
  - JIB Consolidated Mining Company TO Jenkins Vulcan Spring Company (Box 182)
  - Jenney Electric Mfg. Co. TO Johnson Iron Works Dry Dock & Sm Building Company (Box 183)
  - (Lewis D.) Jophnsons & Son Company TO Kalamazoo Building Company (Box 184)
  - Kalamazoo National Bank TO Kansas City Public Service Company (Box 185)
  - Kanasa City Quarries Company TO Kansas City Power & Lighting Company (Box 186)
  - Kansas City Public Service Company TO Kansas City, Wyanootte & NW Railway Company (Box 187)
  - Kansas City Colorado Pacific Railway Company TO Karnstadt (Rudolph) Inc. (Germany) (Box 188)
  - Karnstadt (Rudolph) Inc. (Germany) TO Kelsey-Hayes Wheel Corp. (Box 189)
  - Kelsey Wheel Co. TO Kern Realty Corp. (Box 190)
  - Kerr-Addison Gold Mines Ltd. TO Keystone Watch Case Company (Box 191)
  - Keystone Waterworks Co. TO Kingston Gas & Electric Company (Box 192)
  - Kingston Products Corp. Kruger & Toll Company (Box 193)
  - Kruger & Toll Coampny (Sweden) TO Lackawanna Steele Co. (NY 1902) (Box 194)
  - Lackawanna & Mallney Telephone Company TO Lake Forest Water Company (Box 195)
  - Lake Gas Co. TO Landay Bros. Inc. (Box 196)
  - Lander Electric Lights & Power Company TO Laurel Grove Cemetary Co (Box 197)
  - Laurel Lake Mills TO Leece-Neville Co. (Box 198)
  - Lee Communicatiopns Inc. TO Lehigh Valley Railroads Co. (Box 199)
  - Lehigh Valley Railroad Company (Mortgages) TO Lester, Carter & CO. (Box 200)
  - Lester Engineering Company (Ohio) TO Libby. McNeill & Libby (Box 201)
  - Libby's Hotel Corp. TO Limestone Transportation Corp. (Box 202)
  - Limited Realty Company TO Lincoln Telephone & Telegraph Co. (Box 203)
  - Lincoln Traction Co. TO Liquid Carbonk Corp. (Box 204)
  - Liquid Carbonk Corp., 1927 TO Live Oak Oil & Gas Corp. (Box 205)
  - Live Poultry Transit Co. TO Loan's (Marcus) Theatre Company (Box 206)
  - Lowes Marcus Theatre Ltd. TO Lone Star Land Co. (Box 207)
  - Lone Star Gas Co. TO Long Island Lighting Co. (annual report) (Box 208)
  - Long Island Live Stock Fair Corp. TO Lory Electronics Inc. (Box 209)
  - Los Angele Biltmore Hotel Co. TO Louisiana and Northwest Railroad Co. (Box 210)
  - Louisiana Oxygen Company TO Louisville, New Albanny and Chicago Railroad Co. (Box 211)
  - Louisville and Nashville Railroad Eq. Turst TO Loyal Mining and Leasing Co. (Box 212)
  - Lloyd Scruggs Company TO Lycoming Manufacturing Corp. (Box 213)
  - Lydia Cotton Mills TO Mal Dermid Inc. (Box 214)
  - MacDonald Company TO (Josiah)Macy Jr. Foundation (Box 215)
  - Mad Ox Mines Inc.TO Mamoning Investment Co. (Box 216)
  - Mamoning Savings and Trust Co. TO Malletts Bay Club (Box 217)
  - Mallinckroot Inc. TOManhattan Life Insurance Co. (Box 218)
  - Manhattan Mammota Mining Co. TO Manitoba Power Co. Ltd. (Box 219)
  - Manitoba Railway Co.Maple Valley TO Rural Telephone Company (Box 220)
  - Maplewood Hotel Co. TO Marine Midland Corp. (Box 221)
  - Marine Midland Trust Co. TO The Marsden Co. (Box 222)
  - Marseille Land and Water Power Co. TO Massachusettes Gas Company (Box 223)
  - Massachusettes Investors Growth Stock TO Maxwell Motor Corp. (Box 224)
  - Maxwell Scientific International, Inc. TO McClure Publications (Box 225)
  - McClure's Magazine TO McGran Tire & Rubber Co. (Box 226)
  - McGregor & McIntyre Ltd. TO W.D. McRae Lumber Co. (Box 227)
  - McRare Oil & Gas Co. TO Menraden Oil & Guano Co. (Box 228)
  - Menomnee & Marinette Light & Traction Co. TO Merchants & Manufactures Terminal Inc. (Box 229)
  - Merchant's Metropolitan National Bank TO Merritt's Red Jacket Distillery & Free Warehouse (Box 230)
  - Merritt-Chapman & Scott Corp TO Metropolitan Life Insurance Co. (Box 231)
  - Metropolitan Life Insurance Co. TO Mexican Coal & Coke Co. (Box 232)
  - Mexican Eagle Oil Co., Ltd. TO H.H. Meyer Packing Co. (Box 233)
  - Mexican Coffee Plantation Co. TO Michigan Steele Corp. (Box 234)
  - Michigan Steele Tube Products Co. TO Middle West Corp. (Box 235)
  - Middle West Gas & Electric Co. TO Milbury National Bank (Box 236)
  - Midland United Co. TO Miller Hotel Co. (Box 237)
  - G.L. Miller & CO. TO Milwaukee & Northern Railroad Co. (Box 238)
  - Milwaukee Refrigerator Transit & Car Co. TO Minneapolis Elk Building Co. (Box 239)
  - MI-Medicine Co. Minneapolis Threshing Machine Co. (Box 240)
  - Minneapolis Western Railway Co TO Mirro Aluminum Co. (Box 241)
  - Mirror Films, Inc. TO Mississippi River, Hamburg & Western Railway CO. (Box 242)
  - Mississippi River Power Co. Missouri, Kansas Texas Railway Co. (Box 243)
  - Missouri, Kansas Texas Railway Co. TO Missouri Power & Light Co. (Box 244)
  - Missouri Public Service Co. TO Mohawk Hydro-Electric Co. (Box 245)
  - Mohawk Investment Corp. TO Monangahela Railway Co. (Box 246)
  - Monongahela River R.R. CO. TO Montana Power Transmission Co. (Box 247)
  - Montana Power Co. TO Montreal Locomotive Works, Ltd. (Box 248)
  - Montreal Metropolitan Commission TO Morris & Co. (Box 249)
  - Morriss & Essex Railroad TO Mortgage Guarantee Co. (Box 250)
  - Mortgage Co. of Maryland, Inc. TO Motor Stocter Corp. (Box 251)
  - Motor Transit Co. TO Mountain Lake Corp. (Box 252)
  - Mountain Lion Mining Co., Ltd. TO Munsey Water Supply Co. (Box 253)
  - Municipal Bank of the State of Hessen TO Muscogee Mfg. Co. (Box 254)
  - Muscoy Development Co. TO NSU Motorenwerke Atkiengesellschaft Neckarsulm (Box 255)
  - N. V. Hondelsvereeniging Amsterdam TO Nassau Land Bank (Box 256)
  - Nassau Land & Improvement Bank TO National Bank of Egypt (Box 257)
  - National Bank of Fairfield TO National Casket Co. (Box 258)
  - National Castings Co. TO National Developemeny Co. (Box 259)
  - National Dictograph Co. TO National Gypsum Co. (Box 260)
  - National Hamilton Bank TO National New Haven Bank (Box 261)
  - National Newark Banking Co. TO National Steele Co. (Box 262)
  - National State Bank of Newark, N.J. TO National Stores Investment Co. (Box 263)
  - Navarro Oil Company TO Nevada Central Railway (Box 264)
  - Nevada Central Railway Co. TO New England Co. (Box 265)
  - New England Co. Power System TO New England Southern Corp. (Box 266)
  - New England Southern Mills TO New Jersey Electric Protection Co. (Box 267)
  - New Jersey Fidelity & Loan Co. TO New Orleans National Bank (Box 268)
  - New Orleans Railway & Light Co. TO New York Business Building Corp. (Box 269)
  - New York Butcher's Calf Skin Association TO New York Central & Hudson River Railroad (Box 270)
  - New York Central Railroad TO New York Harbor Dry Dock Corp. (Box 271)
  - New York, Honsatic & Northern R.R. Co. TO New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Co. (Box 272)
  - New York Northern Grain Co. TO New York Sewing Machine Co. (Box 273)
  - New York Shipbuilding Corp. TO New York, Susquehanna & Western Railroad (Box 274)
  - New York, Susquehanna Coal Co. TO New York White Cross Milk Co. (Box 275)
  - New York, Westchester & Boston Railway Co. TO Newport Industries, Inc. (Box 276)
  - Newport Land Trust Co. TO Niagara Land & Fruit Co. (Box 277)
  - Niagra Laundry & Mtf. Co. TO Nipissing Mines Ltd. (Box 278)
  - Nippon Beet Sugar Manufacturing Co. TO Norfolk & Southern Railroad Co (Box 279)
  - Norfolk & Southern Lighting To North American Co. (Box 280)
  - North American Co. TO North American Light & Power Co. (Box 281)
  - North American Loan & Trust Co. TO North Standard Mining Co. (Box 282)
  - North Star Construction Co. TO Northern Indiana Power Co. (Box 283)